fun thing I left off in the first one no
on the day some people pet it tells me
that on the day that we done this on the
Suzuki that a few of you God I am saying
you should have shut your mouth Peter
because Joe is going to tell you exactly
how he done it nearly Gus and you kept
interrupting him what was that did I
interrupt Jesus what was up just tell
him oh that's wrong because all these
interruptions and everything else if I
was gonna tell you I would've told you I
was gonna tell you now ornithology now
he didn't interrupt I wasn't going to
tell you it's out there for years
they've come up with some of the ideas
of what's making some of this stuff work
it's damn frequencies frequencies
all different kinds of frequencies do
these different things and I just played
with one at the present moment generator
kind of fuels that you use catch the how
to get from frequency different timings
different entity that's the drags look
at the delay fuel rails the big fastest
machines are they going from points
condenses in the distributors nope for
now are they going to electronic no
wrong
direction they're going back to not one
magneto they come back to twin Magneto's
eight cylinders sixteen leads but
a sixteen leads into an eighty elevator
and there's screaming the ties to
oblivion and getting most bad that you
can't believe back
to the old Maggie what
are we going to wrong directions
anyway no I was not going to Chili's and
so on and there may be a time I will but
the thing is at the present moment you
won't learn it if I tell you something
and then the other powers out they're
just going to say oh you're full of
which you can do better than setting ice
or whatever I thank you say say
anything you like I don't care if I
mention 4.7 one what's that maybe is 4.7
one sells white seconds so flies over
seconds again parts on the second what
happened to that people now you didn't I
said question is a vehicle where India I
didn't matter I just said four point
seven one four point seven one was a
vehicle running with airfield everything
else on the drag drag and it got buried
because of what I can do no
sound no wheel spin
no g-forces second
straight away buried and people
were at the track it was done on
directory here in Australia and roughly
with you
ran 90 farmers yeah
and there were what three to four
thousand people at the drag track you
actually seen this denier well I saw the
video there yet did you see thousands of
things well I estimated a couple yeah a
couple of thousand people as witnesses
now
there was no flame coming out of it no
CR no flame no fuel no sonic boom right
at the end of the run so
your language on you thank you oh and
I'm interrupting again well we think we
see and what we think we hear or how we
think we understand everything else
sometimes we don't eat
our eyes backwards no the vehicle on the
track was all yes and just a little bit
of what foolish thing yourself coming
out a little exhausted today yeah and
then after the thousands of so people
will counter from 10 to 0 it
looked like then the follower planted
the accelerator after mmm they can with
2-0 any before we
call times he and when he did that call
it accelerator there was a mighty bang
was it a was there Mr O'Shea that
appliable so I I never said this fits
attend um the vehicle never you girl
sort of didn't
wheel stand even real spending it it
just was this white stuff will come out
the exhaust pipe word you might call odd
player steam something like that didn't
want you know didn't catch a light just
got gone backwards there's no flame and
I thinking then there was no noise the
whole track and nobody well
one kid snapped his neck winner that's
what you see one little kid just solely
did nobody was type of a cheer what you
see know what I know it's I will spend
no that's my no realistic nice
disappointing
to get four point seven months seconds
and the world record still stands job um
did he last year you read and everything
else with a few others are getting down
to cause I knew it'd be getting down
into the force sevens now but way up
there getting closer but
in that time 1995
nobody in Australia or anywhere else as
far as I know not in Australia
definitely had it come anywhere near to
five seconds and over five slices from
the world record of that stage was about
5.30 that's drag racing know what and it
went up against a twin jet is that
correct first-run twin jet twin
fifty-five thousand horsepower jet
vehicle it the jet vehicle was halfway
down the track this one was finished and
the twin jet is recorded there any girls
to doing six point six four seconds 253
mile now out of a jet vehicle with flame
with Lloyds with no massive mining
boys here back you know a jet and that
was twin 55,000 horsepower jets and this
vehicle first running had no feel nope
no wheelie bars hey big tires no it
was finished hmm no record on well the
escort Bateman
[Laughter]
there's raw
energy if you want to look at it and
applying it to power source you want to
go add the NC R or Energy go and look at
some of the rails some of the massive
power that they're climbing driving out
of so called fuels tonight
and you don't do that under veto on the
right that few conversations so
there's clean mention of pouring some
water into a flooded Creek and cleaning
up the water you're not supposed to do
that no
but what happens same
thing again you line up water with a
right frequency to lined up back into
nature the way that God had planned it
near you girls and so on and it cleanse
itself you go ahead there to a river it
sets in you go I'm not down too many
trees you can do all these things storms
have frequencies you want to look at
them and every even if you look at the
rainbows
and everything else before and after a
storm you get them the colors are
backwards to two rainbows in a storm and
everything else colors which are
frequencies you know that line door back
to back then not stack and stacking the
same they unpack the back so it's
reversed charge so reversed everything
you know you straighten out the rivers
putting them and everything else in what
God had built there with an S and you
stuff your orders you
know kidney shape these flow forms and
everything else are built into the rocks
by the way that the water flows enduring
the kid kidney S or a figure eight
sideways shape and they carve themselves
and delete a cleaner bore it showed the
other thing if you add charged water
into the cars coolant system what
happens when
I do that now score cooled yeah I see
you put it in
the actual charged watering seems to
clean it up that's been your experience
yeah well you're rusting and all you all
the other things in there you girls are
sort of altered in your vehicle runs as
far as out there on the internet before
years ago and actually did these things
instead they have difference they can
run a charge water into the matter files
I've been putting the carburetors I can
put it into radiators and things like
that and get on temperature
differences in the firing ability of the
engines it's different frequencies
different alignments and everything else
do alter estate off heat and cold so
it's a transmutation
joke where you put a product it might be
oil or something like that in the cell
and it continues to grow the oil or
whatever is that normal you
may make it yeah
it's nature you want to go back to the
Bible first page and everything else out
of water come all the so again how many
minerals how many plants how many
everything else are in the solid ground
because everything we're in every bit of
that here in water and you can either
pull them out or not just scientists may
not know how you can put some of these
things back into order 101 of them salt
sugar things like that you can stir it
with a couple of stirs solar stuff take
it straight in dissolve it get it back
out how
quickly to go in you should be able to
get it back out the same how much sludge
it shitty lucky stuff to use that we're
buying applying electrical charges and
everything else to normal water to get a
little grain of salt back out back it's
a black bar brownish sludge but then
when you dry it all down and take all
this off ready end up with a small
amount okay
so um we just haven't figured out how
God blue chip
he does things very you know simple
very
simple to take some sugar and dissolve
it into a cup of tea get it back it up
okay you
should be able to get it back out as
simple how does he take your um your
water your sort of your liquid water and
take it up there and disguise they call
it piss it bag in turns
it into some other energy something else
very quickly very easy you don't have to
boil water to turn it into steam to
evaporate up into the air to soak all
make the flavor soak all right on you hi
you got to at the end of freezing Carl
morning go down the river and look at
any water hole Larry the dam start
freezing cold it's evaporating more
visibly can what you see in the hot day
oh so
does that tell you that
declaration heat oil steam no doesn't
different way and it also has a
different charge so you'll run your cold
juice in the mornings and everything
else carry a nitrogen or negative charge
but you're here and you would steam and
everything else in the middle of the day
what is hot and does it this other way
of evaporating as a positive charge or
vice versa
different ways you know it's been known
by men in cars out there to get a lot
more miles per gallon off that cold unit
through the night your car runs a hell
of a lot smoother and less fuel with
less acceleration when the temperature
drops when the cloud comes over at
nighttime so they called you in the
morning got the trees and now look at
the flaming breakers just one little
flare comes over and they then start
making horse now because of its changing
their arrows are changing the charge of
the frequency and they just yuan they're
gone if it does it to them massive
depressions of students but they got to
make the horsepower what we're doing
your vehicle with less maybe not as
pronounced
but it's still doing it good
enough thank you Joe the material
used as a spacer
[Music]
in the material in the in the cells that
are being produced at the moment I don't
know I don't produce any cells at the
moment I don't know what yous are all
using all I do know that answer is
anything that you find which is a
insulator
for your electricity which is AC and DC
is really a conductor in another way it
just is turned around in a way that is
lining up so that your electricity won't
go through it might bite you much short
answerable okay so a insulator
is really no conductor in another way
conducts some materials that we have but
user trying to use insulators
which you know obviously insulators for
AC and DC that we know of today really
using for AC and DC we're going to use
in the north and south pole or aluminum
you know is that in our electricity
local south yeah
apparently positive or negative okay and
um what happened east and west what
happened up up and down what happened
every other degree of in this earth as
well we only call electricity come from
North myself that we the only way that
our energy feels or magnetism czar or
things align up
so
what's actually happening is that in
these cells you put these plates in
called neutral plates and if you watch
this stuff the electricity don't go the
same as your normal electricity went
it's it goes different angles so if it's
turned around so just turn around to a
ninety degree okay a ninety degree
compared
to your normal metals of choosing there
we go jumping through the water that way
and you have a piece of insulator
in between and that's the electricity
now because it's gone on a different
angle Tesla found this out with a
calculator right the coil you found out
that your positive and negative you go
one way around cause and head back out
the other way but even out with this new
energy coming out the other end as well
a different thing altogether and it's
not using the other see it changes
alters the estate frequency all the rest
so what
I believe is happening is the
arrangement that is so-called geocells
and never call them had ever done
making me done build them and doesn't
show me done sell them and he doesn't do
anything else with it nothing don't use
it yourself now she's something you
found is turning the frequencies around
and then your nell insulator is right in
the demo if you watch some of these
tapes of what some of this stuff you
fellas hear put themselves together
which you come where's all the
in the world or yourselves or your
insulators where is the stuff going when
it breaks down in the water with this
low voltage DC charging self where to go
well it's not staying in the water some
plates it's actually electroplating to
you should ground electroplating you're
found out what kind of frequency that
you actually applied these minerals
pulling them out the water turning
around and actually making them go and
stick to your plates you
see stainless is not supposed to stain
in him over to dust if you do it a
certain way and if you pull it out of
the water where's it going what's coming
out of the water but you didn't see it
in the water in the first place
to the surface some goes to the plate
some goes to the plastics or perspecsys
some goes to your rods so I'm going to
positive some go to negative rods
something I go to then not positive or
negative goes to the surface leave it on
the surface for a little while there you
go shut your cell down just leave it the
shits in the top where to go the
dents that falls out straight through
and goes to the bottom okay
go back and turn your machine back on
where's it go from the bottom to the top
and
[Music]
when you get all this stuff from this X
of it and some of them just keep making
a making a make and making the ask about
reproduction the things that everything
where'd you get this stuff from what's
breaking them sometimes some of the
cells aren't breaking down this
stainless is not breaking down the
celery's and breaking in the insulators
I'll break it down but you're making it
just heaps of stuff where
is it what is it mad cup of sugar that
you said to me result
as you study me I'm sort of his dinosaur
P don't believe in anything I believe
in creation look these things are
created Joey
next question hi Josh can you first
describe in detail and in layman's terms
with
the satellite and first oh it's cool
tell me - no easy to explain
the wiring configuration that allows the
engine to run on cold
implosion mo it's my understanding all
the components are already in the end on
the engine please tell us step by step
what to do thank you
No and give you a couple of examples
otherwise dattara to nature naturally
ten and engines we
fire our timing before top dead center
on the compression everything else as we
told out of the exposure notes if
it exploded there with some of these
engines which are going nachus three
four or five degrees before top dead
center six degrees even some of these
recast on engines are going twenty-two
up to thirty right to roll the link to
eighty degrees before top dead center
with no seal on there with this stuff
which is really nice position especially
halfway up the ball right
your normal engine if it exploded before
the piston hit the top what do you think
the piston is going to go where do you
think your back wheels are going to go
definitely not forward then
I go backwards it's going to stop it
drive it backwards it doesn't do that
your piston okay what do you mechanics
out there saying we get your head inside
the silver and check it out don't care
what you say what happens is there's an
implosion occurs when you set off your
spark inside the cell or done detonate
the engine anyway and blow your fuels
it's not stuck so it actually goes to
the top of the silver and it doesn't
start expanding out there he goes till
it goes over top dead cells then there's
a big expansion when
you slow is that they go and check out
what Val bounces off
our bounces inside folks I mean the
valves the Pistons and everything else
going too fast
stuffed a few flamin our head engineers
and people
with that idea to use our
bounces creating a as
it's not an implosion such a vacuum your
um your Pistons is gone past top dead
center down the power straight and is
run out of what's in there and
got enough to get to the boss because
on your upstroke you've got you've got
blow by at the top when it fires near
you've got massive expansion ever once
it's one of the cold imploding engines
yeah look at um so some
sterling has a hot air motor but there
are the opposite motors which are calls
liquor motors and there's also other
motors out there which are called us
liquor motors exam on liquor later
actually runs on the cold side they
actually wait till my piston goes right
to the bottoms and everything else and
everything cools and then because it's
already got to the coal
she's such a piston up then I use the
powers expansion stroke they use these
cold clothes inside of it you've known
the Olympics chilly mix what actually
happens in the engine is at the top of
the stroke and everything else big
expansion big he big everything else and
then decays down the ball but you've
lost most everything to get you from the
top of the piston to the top of the
board to the bottom of the piston she
get so far down runs out shanyna creates
a suction in the smallest part is the
Bell dish think of a double bells ring
something that you around
you know you slow down by putting up
extra load on it but leave you leave
your engine stock standard with a stock
standard values and everything else and
you might be the I bounce into five
thousand readers don't put tell by one
so
that term I'll give you helms firstly
reach more pressure in the balls how
fast can you go now okay
well you don't bow bound to high sales
and registers you might now bounce out
since a.m. nor not ten you're doubling
the speed of the valve I leave
you're done you put more in the silver
so
means that this is going up and down
faster by dozens and you um and you
don't have it so to standard out what
was bouncing at foster as it moves away
it was for the upper to burn a
supercharger what are you doing you can
pump a right up to a speed anything else
because it's allowing extra extra more
than the turbo into that and the small
valve within of the valves with a small
valve spring stands and there he goes
you might now do somewhere between 10 to
20,000
ribs and
um still doesn't do it and valves
they're cutting valves now on angles
they're not straight up and down over
the top of the Pistons and lunch I bow
bouncer mostly run straight up and down
over top of the Pistons first suction
your
angle of you suck and everything else
just diamond shapes and so on some ways
one way schools on the head of the
piston the servicing in a way is just
smaller least amount what's on the
invitation this is this big strong rod
crankshaft knew the minute smallest
weakest point is at the tip balance runs
out like when you're pissing goes over
the top dead center you got no more
virtual push you're running out you push
them down by the extension of your gases
prevent conflict is that turn into coal
pretty recently okay with the shortest
of the shortest edge it's this big that
long the whole that lives there
using the enclosure sizes from red-hot
to coal don't
check them so concern from Red Hots to
freezing cold and then clothes suck up
so what's going to do in your engines it
closes down and creates it back here and
check it out someone gone right into
that now you just look at the context
okay how much you need to put into a
ball to get the piston from top to
bottom whatever
the size the engine is close your vows
can press it up you lose some here's
past your rings explode to the top lose
some more down the power stress doesn't
need to take the piston from the top to
the bottom what you had in there in the
first place you know you're insane a lot
of real numbers you might have more push
you think because of expansion explosion
and teeth but that rapidly just closes
down as a piston drops away so wrap it
so when you got me a hole and doesn't
things closed down and contract very
quickly and become so as it has intense
so
your piston is doing it naturally
imploding
with the frequencies first to get your
piston to the top it's on your
compression stroke and then exploding
and broiling down the boss and then at
the other end you haven't got enough so
she creates a vacuum that's not in
places into the vacuum it's okay and Oh
slows down and sucks the smallest thing
opens see you build more isn't it you
guys go down fit further you go down
faster let's see my most secret license
employing engines well
I suppose
Commodores are actually using it I'm not
saying you're going to use positive to
this nearing the girls but Commodores
are using the negative side to explode
your gases and expansion and thinking
else blow the silver under compression
so using the positive side of the coil
at six degrees a 4-top exhaust and it
actually includes it now
include are using the positive to
actually drive a motor under compression
engine compression chambers same as we
do in the heat and you know on their
negative side so maybe that's is
it a combination using up one and using
up the other
I didn't say I'm just giving you some
little set you know we're asking a
question I should know I know but I try
what have these different things that
are occurring at everything else you
know Commodores aren't firing positive
and negative twice in the same Selma at
the same time actually driving the other
selfies okay and they do different
things but doesn't science teacher even
though they can't apply themselves don't
they teach you for every action there is
an opposite equal reaction so
if negative exploded what positive do
but if England positive X place what is
negative 2 and
then how do they get it to happen anyway
what
do you got to do to make implosions well
did you know that some of these gases
actually do it anyway water turn these
hydrogen and oxygen more oxygen want to
pee why were laying yellow fine boom
explosions get rid of your cheatin
stories
it get ready on you
the more that you get my together you
get rid of you the lesson pollution that
you have in the water in other words
caustic soda the less pollutants you
have in the water and the less of one
guess compared to the other hydrogen or
oxygen the crisper the cracks and some
of these bubbles you play the cells in
that some of these bubbles actually
don't explode they turn finally
exploding into implosion
and your ears have been with the
pressure and everything else for sound
airy take pressure that's what you
realize you're doing you got some
pudding posing ones check your head you
got ringing in your head you got hurting
in your ears and so on my den candy or
anything for ages and laws so
she in place so normal water in nature
turning into these things just two
things anyway it creation I'm saying
this could
you explain enjoy theoretically what
happens when the two frequencies collide
we
deadly in front of the camera with my
face on your face okay cool yeah yeah
come on have a go energies I don't know
I'll bring it good very feast to
official what I missed it sorry I was
similar there was a question too many
Gees of what comes
um well it's in the in the clarity
within the engine unfortunately the
printer that I printed this out with mr.
bit so
please explain the details what happens
theoretically when the two presidencies
collide and how they create the
synergies and what the similarity that
message where I'm still missing what
you're really talking about but I'll go
by this did you know that your your car
is producing clear different energies
you know in a bore anyway naturally to
create an X plus and also two
differences and you have two different
electricity's positive and negative and
so
on my dad you've got AC and DC the DC
space to run around all your car
everywhere and so on but at the coil
system into a seems that AC is jumping
across the spark plugs but when they're
supposed to happen they tell you in the
ball you have just something
once you know all these wet petrels or
gases and air and everything else sort
of does what so
I scream punching users because you
punch them in v1 the Alex whoever hits a
ground first in how big of a hurry you
get a spontaneous different reactions
okay sometimes if
you run head-on okay
you run head on to something you you
have a big
energy either heat or bang crash don't
move okay good
next night how do you take one piece of
water one piece of wire on your battery
positive
on one india battery negative on the
other and you're dead straight piece of
wire just touch it on both what do you
got sure dead sure and I hope on
different
how do you get the dead short not to
take place because of these two actually
supposedly running
into each other or funny each other or
whatever they're doing not liking each
other and producing what about our water
heater big spike and burn the end of the
terminal of your battery if it's got
enough keep their help your
one piece of water what do you do to it
on just
caught up grab your finger Cinderella
wrap it cannot touch the same one on
dear battery what happens why your top
as
quick big dead sure on the end of the
terminals is there a certain amount of
windings that you can actually do on
that piece of wire to stop the dead
short the while you're not is
in a milk what Neil allows them to
actually run straight past each other
and don't interfere with each other
because they are whelmed does
it have to be wound around offender oh
you
Repertory Theater no I've got your hands
up career Asura well
it's a finger and then test will found
out morning and two different ways at
the same time does a different things
and winding it same way you go grab a
screwdriver you want to magnetize it
what do you do want it one way and help
it on but put a piece of metal in
between your piece of wire and touch it
on the battery and your why does indeed
shorter as you just want a key opens
your screwdriver becomes magnetized
because the energy goes there okay and
if you want it the other way what
happens well the screwdriver is north
part 1 ending to tell Holly other
implants if you won the piece of wire
the other ways
the North and South Korean jeans okay
and
what do you got in the middle you
screwdriver ain't nothing well
I wasn't a random only finger
or anything else what
Abed Oh number
warnings no I can't count on your way to
school all right no I knew that just
ease your fingers Jess
Seventeen's
and
have a look something then off Swedish
ways there's
an order when you speak lad there nearly
a girl see anybody religious everybody
and don't have to be religious
non-religious about the evidence you
ever notice that in the Bible there's a
princess if you know the Bible can be
read like them you know there's chapters
and verses in the Bible forget them but
you do know Z or every chapter every
verse has a number on it and the numbers
aren't that high and all the numbers why
not all the numbers never change one
number has a name and a reason for that
number and they all fall under that all
the way from one in the other new nature
does the same nature you want to check
something go out to a Christian
bookstore or an order if see pain vay
any book it is only a little small book
at that cost very much it is on the seal
of God forget
if you don't believe in God don't care
go and have a look at it as such to see
what what he's talking about she talks
about planting flowers fight poisons
safe things to eat in the Bible as well
numbers numbers to God numbers for good
numbers for bad numbers for going
forward numbers for going backwards
numbers for like things numbers for
wrong feet okay all things have a
numbering order tool you get them out of
all of what they can do not what you
wanted it do
it was what the order is and it will do
what they always amazes okay and if you
want a other border and the border done
is inside Minitab water you might just
put it in this arrangement
you now call a new order and
it is now doing something for you which
might
in another way same order fight against
you might not be what you're after might
not be what you want and as they put
these two together say he's trying to
give me a way here new here you go so we
won one screwed over one way through
this and touch it on the battery we
wanted another one the same way for
another piece of water put on less for
those two screwdrivers now this line
usually marry each other anything else
to Willy sometimes punch each other in
the nose or they push each other apart
or they attract to each other it's
different arrangement two different
things in the order that they're in and
you can make all these orders and
arrangements to do pull push expired
employees you know go not go electrocute
you or not electrocute you okay your
frequencies polarities the
science teaches through reaction there's
not as an equal reaction so give
it this way it's a car supposed to or if
it kind of does run on petrol then sighs
steady static are shrewd also you have a
little knot around people they wrote
apparently is the law and she beat
spider lord sesa vengers will run on
something else okay ask yourself this
question if you are looking at it as
such water water
itself he
doesn't burn doesn't actually not and it
doesn't if you drink it knock your brain
stupid so you go for round a gram to
most
people okay distilled water and
distilled alcohol what's the difference
so all liquids are 99.99999%
fine h2o which is water and invest
elation what is the process for
distilling water distilling alcohol
exactly the same and what is left behind
in distillation every single thing you
heat it up it evaporates turns into h2o
steam has been
a contentious gggg and then falls back
down is purified
work yeah that's
the same process forever and you put the
two in a glass and you can't tell their
difference by looking at it what
is the difference between alcohol and
water and I scientifically there isn't
any except break it all down what
alcohol
amends
and drinking alcohol knock your socks
off and alcohol evaporates at a
different rate and I'll call you for
putting you Karen alcohol burn in car
engine running a sauna pit
alcohol is 99.9999% what
up and you put water into a diesel
engine my pistons don't go up and down
anymore and
you pour water into a electric spark
engine letter and person
does keep it up in here oh yeah
but you know you put water into a into
an engine and don't run on their water
but you put alcohol in an engine and
ducks even in diesel engine you put then
your oil and all that stuff and
runs they
mix it right once the diesel do put out
our screens is flipping it off and use
you guys bank much the screams are too
fast perpetual into diesel until engine
positive starts right ghost stick diesel
into a petrol engine was a do well
compression
ratio is a little bit out knocks its
head off
lots of things and clubs blows a lot of
smoke because and
what do you do with your car they stop
your car from gonna turn this back off
stick
these on into a petrol engine and build
up your compression shave you love you
appreciated turn your sparkle for it to
do keeps going have
to high compression in a electric petrol
spark engine too much compression turn
your key off what does it do with petrol
Lauren it keeps going pull
the battery it keeps going pull the
distributor off keeps going lie because
it's flipping diesel in a column because
of the compression while
using the spark in an engine for is
because of the low compression ratio of
the stuff that you're evaporating and
burning alcohol
evaporates differently than what water
does water cools you alcohol kills you
faster with airmobile yes
that boats passed on yep and leaves you
a colder right behind drink
it not your brain out somebody said this
is glycol Joe who
judge
to it in a certain way along then
actually live it in front of the good
water in a bet
as
I was I said these guys were just in
front of all these people on everything
else and it was drinkable water that was
given to all these peoples okay what's
the difference between watering alcohol
only
a frequency of something you know in
that bottle if you don't believe there
he goes his guy called Jesus if there
was a God who Jesus and so on and what
did he do in this so-called little story
they wrote a wedding run out of plunk
growing out linear one Shaylee they all
come to Jesus the miracle guy they
said we had a plot when they just go to
store a bike wouldn't your job ok that's
it chops up I'm sure say they said what
we gonna do well
were you telling me for I'm gonna wanna
you know make it a 1 alcohol living he
goes but we've got this wedding on army
run out of plonk and Jesus got pestered
that much he said well go out and get
five zeros or older go Philip oh that
was in dress number brought him back in
now what do you do aash I don't go to
Jerusalem hooked it up to the clover the
jail cells first office everybody anyway
what did he do he just said now pour it
out
oh yeah I'm gonna go whirring well the
story is the story is that when they
poured it out there was the best tasting
wine out and the reason what the people
said in your sweet air is that stupid
people
we go to a wedding they feed all these
guides the good wine first give them all
a bit Plaza then give me the
because another what they were drinkin
it's a strange wedding because of this
story they gave us a shitty stat well is
all right line but ya got us plastered
first and then make out the best some
stranger on with these guys that was a
story all he did was what I didn't use
anything in touch up they've
looked at a moto stuff what's he playing
i dr. Emoto call him Cosimo oh I did
okay hello
I never
even memories NATO calling cosy by now
anyway mo day uses a water crystal which
is the format of water and everything
else and what happens people's mind just
thinking acting doing writing thinking
good thinking bad what is it what
happens to the water crystal trying to
find it they'll go and look at the stuff
you never seen it from a beautiful
crystal water Christmas everything else
eternity to our black messy beauty
distorted crap that's if you lie they
kick you right the wrong thing that you
can do the wrong alignment the water has
a memory the water knows when you're
lying the water is a what do you call it
a truth teller now I am I speak because
if you tell a lie and you go to water
crystal they're turning your horrible
big black penis so it's a pretty cool
defy me good morning is it good on you
divine divine very high you believe in
intuition I want to crap and believe in
Korea deploy an inspiration or order or
linemen who died huh
Joe what happened here what
are you learning
I'm done
um these are called rattlesnake eggs
rattlesnake
never come out of this but
on rattlesnake eggs they tell you
rattlesnake later on the
magnetism and this has just been lined
up a different way go get yourself the
kids ones why they kids good science
don't want you to know what they do they
actually take the to
pulse of what our normal magnetic field
is which is on life each end they find
it through on the damp side and
then instead of when we rotate one
around instead of rappelling off this
thing's you know we built I'll go ran
ran ran then they still stick and you
turn them around a different way they
put full pulse Python 22 L sincere and
that was until you got a hold of it no
no these without me no but you explained
it beautifully and they were the other
ones just to stuff it up
this
is interesting you know why this is
interesting these are really
around around
cuz he said they've been around here for
a while so he's earth there's a question
in the bottle it
says she's
not really a question as such but it's
good question for you trying
to fire recent corner of that it's
real easy to find the fires the corner
just tell you the viruses yeah look what
you've done to the magnet turn no look
what happened was a God took the best of
the best out of Eden which is called
this earth and he's stuck in the far
eastern corner of a circle something
called the Garden of Eden fire
eastern corner of a circle there
he planted all the best of the best and
there he stuck means circle
earth find the fire is the funny
thing is looks like somebody found that
here some
way
because it don't want to go until
you get to the other side and then this
circles push your way we
power through the middle it's
funny innit you mean somebody Paulo put
a polarizer in everything since these
one stands for feeder you rotate them
and they don't throw away but other
magnets do that's just telling you that
one way that you line up a magnet you
can do it one way and another way that
you likkle
photos okay
no I like to think that there's more
policy your name anyways and one day's
here you think that you only got north
is our part okay but I'm them there you
can find four holes on one where'd you
get the other holes from because they're
not enormous it they're
not good is it and maybe go as you want
to push away they're not opposite hot
yes and when you avoid too much you get
then you get a heap more pop you get
them back to me when you turn them
they're kind of bastards yes and you
don't have pulse you have polls on the
sides multiples you need rocks holes on
the ends which you never had before and
they don't see what these are called
here the rebels in the crackle that
is bouncing pulse
when you move us towards each other
actually they saline but they actually
just switching to us directly it
making this sound which is a hollow
the social funny
bounces be
the frequencies so that's why they call
a rattlesnake
is because that might be like a
rattlesnake I'll throw
them up in the end I do the fighting and
always to show that you shoot a just
wrong
yeah that's up for
every action there's always a little
Ridge everything
will get Emily on Danny right well guys
neons would don't take anybody it does
different
them if
you feel some
field of metal that's why lets you get
to see where the fields are future oh
there's another two single pole major
that's last night this is
how good it huh yeah by the tracks just
two
of the guys done something different now
we use can play with all these I'm that
should if you sit and play with them
everything else explain different ways
different fields which is north and
south pole gives you your positive and
negative positive negative it's north
and south north and south your AC and DC
electricity it seems to be a few more
this one of those registered on your
counters world
look we only tested with a flat piece of
page with the iron filings tips on top
we're not actually looking at it in a
360 degree okay Geiger counters what are
they readers radioactivity or vibration
force extortion of summers how long did
it make these how long did it take each
government taking scientists and
everything else to actually pull this a
couple of different metals to pieces and
end up with radioactive with seconds
they called with the pieces strong
shakes for every action there's an
opposite and equal reaction how
long to take to create it protects how
long should you take to remove it
so with this use myself of this course
hmm done
that one so
inside your timers weren't even
interested in of removing radioactivity
in seconds they
created like
thousand years the have
they been around a few years to actually
find out that that actually diminishes
them some
of the our scientism wrong tradition
explained to the full debris metal I'm
not going
has enabled time for supposed
aggressiveness and all the angles or
options that you possess within it same
as your cat same as water it's
all I give me the water necessary what's
a maker well at least I know you is
called Jose I kept looking back at it -
in the mirror yeah
I keep looking at him and see what he
looks like and I never remember what he
looks like ever every time I look at him
is different excuse me anyway all the
people is put a frequency into the h2o
which actually made the h2o burns
and also evaporate
differently and also cool differently
and also like run in an engine so it
doesn't have the same ability as our
cosmic in finding water
Des Moines but
they're warning about that you visit
shown properly job they
come back and show me what they can do
the solutions are my still no James I
don't have to do anything you don't and
thank you for sharing that with us today
is that all the solutions no now there's
still another eight to go you ready
honey
Cleveland or is a quick one nice what's
a quick lesson baby on there yet Alex
chunks result back here are we got
ringing yeah she's
definitely she's coming back
is there anything you'd like to share
with she'll
marry the other night or any toe what he
said you are machine I got my money -
sure I'll say me they can't date as
you can put the money in good ones
running off Florida nearly go so I'm not
doing it so I'm not seeing it I'm just
trying it's pretty up there is a lot of
bushes out of it so start
checking out really what easy idea what
actually happens and the thing is I care
what you do and I'm not interested in
doing so
go on the praiser Gloria don't your
money and I don't want to be known for
this stuff and I really don't care where
you get it all your days I didn't do it
for you kind of help that didn't do it
for you other people took it out the
other people call the Jay cells near I
didn't so I'm happy enough just to step
away all the threats under Sun never
stop okay
I didn't get them to kill me so I chose
and when
you were good enough in yourself and
satisfied
in yourself to say that you haven't got
any dependence and
dependency all I knew these things in
your life and you can just give them up
and walk away from and don't care of
anything and be free then doesn't matter
they're not buying it nobody's
gonna buy me and nobody's going to force
the media narrative case such and tell
maybe so on you know I mean people could
try you know but they're not so here's
what I mean because I don't have these
problems in them I just go out even
though I've got my money I go out for
petrol Monica and then all these
government people or who is or else
don't want to you know dark don't want
us to run around on whatever we were
supposed to know about run around on
well they're not going to catch me doing
he said look I'm supposed to do what
they want me to do which is put pepper
in the about no one catch me doing
anything else so then they can't dump on
me they can't charge
won't take me car because our fingers
don't eat never carry the moment so we
can't take that so
my thing is I've got a wife and a baby
which I class is not dependent as Co
people with me and I depends on them for
their love and attention and I suppose
that they depend on me my baby depends
on me to feed and change it's nasty and
so on so I do it lovingly
willingly and stuff everything else
what's going to feel without money
included people offer me jobs or
anything else stuff it obvious you
haven't got any money but you do this
job and you can get this amount of money
and you can get stuff Mackenzie
now your wife needs me now and I don't
need you
or the job or anything else and
be free to say that doesn't matter all
these tapes all these cells all these
things all these thousands and thousands
of sites on the internet all these
people playing with this I really don't
care because I care about something else
and it's not important to me what you
play with or what you do but I don't
like to see so many people getting led
down the wrong track so I'll try I don't
have a need of it but this takes you to
try
some
of the things you think you're running
on you
know some of the people who put up a big
fight to say petrol and all these things
run cars nearly girls you're
not always correct it might happen that
this reaction happens with petrol and
also happens with a lot of things and
your natural car preg nice and cold
Diesel's the artificial
so if it does that and then you can
finally tune that without the petrol
look at that move with some of the other
concepts when they do not fit on what
they come up with they
had many many many feet
go back to y'all come actualizing slidin
can't agree go back and sit in the
library and chase up some of these
things from the past when they had to
find something else to get around you
want to fix everything get back to a
horse no
pollution oh yes either risotto to me
thing yeah and they'd grass that's it
then your step in it then there do step
in and
you didn't get there as fast as you want
to get there now so important while
you're trying to go so fast you get out
there to color and you go so fast you
get in that road somebody else is gone
just as fast the other direction or face
or maybe there bang you did you don't go
anywhere now ah yes
you do how fast you want to do some
of these things so Joe you've also
filled people no
I got your people now will they hear
themselves through the assistance that
you've been your body by God and nature
natural is being lined up to heal itself
and stay away forever you
polluted a bit it door to be sooner you
stick the wrong things into it and doors
or sooner it gets you out of shape and
out of order and out of living nothing
diseases
and everything else we find brand new
ones every day what is it it's only
because you either ate the wrong food
again and got out a frequency out of
alignment around something else in your
body reacts to it different reaction and
says here take this okay because she's
just there is an order but you're out so
what is the order every single thing in
your body is 100% in alignment of a
frequency electricity not big faults not
begins it's a moment of a new energy
what God uses it's not your magnetism
ac/dc electricity is your body's a power
plants your brain is all electric your
brain runs all the things in your body
but every atom in your body every atom
is a nuclear power plant if you want to
say they said but I don't take nuclear
it's a powerful thing well new is just
unclear isn't then one thing on your
body gets out of line one atom gets out
of alignment or something because you
don't something to or does it need to
get back into honor line up the
frequencies again so all it's happening
is that some way that some
people come up with medicines or
minerals or
things like that to actually realize
what was animal know what they put out
anyway will you put it so
find the things I'll put them back in
there I just found found that different
things like the
water cells can be battery car batteries
which are DC flat line transformers
converted back from AC to DC can
actually line you up other people have
found AC helping people line them up and
okay you're putting your electrics or
interacting with your electrics in your
body back into some sort order or you
can do other things make it worse do the
wrong for you put down the border
apparently so I'll be told and it's
happening that we've seen that nearing
us that got reports from all around the
world as well that some people have put
these cells together and it's like very
sick and nauseous and some people felt
really really good and some people have
been blacked out for twenty minutes or
more by just turning a cell on okay and
what's it doing what what are you what
are you built there to to do the people
know I've had people being here by
touching the cup it's just touch the car
the card dies when that happens but this
whatever being generated goes into the
person make it heal with many things
just
quick and again move it anyway I'm I'm
out of another time if you're real exact
your electric every inch of you which it
is every sense every feeling every touch
and everything else is frequencies along
and everything else if something is that
of a long what do you need to do put it
back into alignment how do you do that
when you go figure out what you're in
what you're running off and then go and
play with it and put it back the way it
was figure out how it was in the first
place that's pretty hard to doing so
these things is it just I stumble across
a few things we've put some people back
into order sometimes
have to learn they said you know no I'm
silly I just go out and do it I go out
in faith that thing called you know and
go and say it's kind of the person is
going to be only under here and though
no matter what disease ago it seems like
it's they
got killed and I get it again I don't
know once you try it yourself that's
what the Bible told you to do Jesus told
you to go out there in faith and so on
like that open is claiming God and it
happens he says go and tell that
mountain there to pluck itself I've got
a plan itself in the ocean it'll do it
and
you're thinking I'm silly don't know
what you want to do that for okay but if
you had faith which is this thing inside
you which is no doubt whatsoever you
know I'd have to doubt if I said walk
over there till around go no no any of
the wrong thing you just say to me over
the beach let's go surfing anywhere
you courage the mountain there say teens
I can ride thanks Joe and thank you guys
for listening yeah they'll do their
tight end see you next time maybe hook
up good
on you I'll give you as a clap for doing
what you're doing and thinking the way
you're thinking okay you need to patent
the back to you for what you're doing
and how you're thinking and you're
actually questioning the authority and
the law I'm not saying the police I'm
saying the law of science or mathematics
a law of cars or a law of electricity or
something you're questioning if you
question it began to come up with a
different answer a different way of
doing things that's good it's all what
happened with me it's all what happens
to other people question
everything there's no law to anything
good
[Music]